Guide To the University Of California, Santa Cruz Contemporary Classical Collection ARS.0103
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 7" reels, 118 audiotape reel(s)
  - Jean Nandi harpsichord recital. Bowen: Toccatina., 1970; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; stereo; two track] (Box 10, Reel 75)
    Frescobaldi, Girolamo, 1583-1643. Toccate e partite d'intavolatura, libro 2o. Aria detta la Frescobalda. Nandi, harpsichord. KPFA benefit concert. December 24, 1970.
    Bowen, York, 1884-1961. Siciliano and toccatina, piano, op. 128; arranged. Saxby, harpsichord. October 10, 1970.
    Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667; Frescobaldi, Girolamo, 1583-1643; Couperin, François, 1668-1733; Bowen, York, 1884-1961; Saxby, Joseph, 1910-1997; Nandi, Jean
  - Copland; Harris; Mozart; Scriabin; Stravinsky, circa 1968; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips; stereo; four track] (Box 10, Reel 76)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 537, D major. De Larrocha, piano; Cleveland Orchestra, Ancerl, conductor.
    Harris, Ross, 1945- Symphonies, no. 3.
    Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Symphonies, no. 2, op. 29, C minor. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Semkow, conductor. First United States performance.
    Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Billy the Kid. Suite. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Copland, conductor.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Ode, orchestra. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Copland, conductor.
    Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Inscape. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Copland, conductor. Tanglewood Festival. 1968.
    Boston Symphony Orchestra; Ančerl, Karel, 1908-1973; Harris, Roy, 1898-1979; Larrocha, Alicia de; Cleveland Orchestra; Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990; Semkow, Jerzy, 1928-j; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915
  - Henkemans; Kraft; Lampugnani; Ravel; Shostakovich, circa 1963; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 77)
    Henkemans, Hans. Sonatas, piano.
    Lampugnani, Giovanni Battista, 1706-approximately 1786. Superbo di me stesso, from Meraspe. Horne, mezzo-soprano; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra, Lewis, conductor.
    Kraft, William. Silent boughs.
    Shostakovich, Dmitriĭ Dmitrievich, 1906-1975. Concertino, pianos (2), op. 94.
    Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Duet, violin, cello. Plummer, violin; Colf, cello. 1963.
    Kraft, William; Lampugnani, Giovanni Battista, 1706-approximately1786; Colf, Howard; Henkemans, Hans; Shostakovich, Dmitriĭ Dmitrievich, 1906-1975; Horne, Marilyn; Plummer, Stanley; Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Lewis, Henry, 1932-1996
  - Allende; Arnold; Bennett; Botto; Davies; Gow; Lutosławski; Skalkottas; Stravinsky; Wood, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips] (Box 11, Reel 78)
    Lutosławski, Witold, 1913-1994. Postludes, orchestra.
    Allende, Pedro Humberto, 1885-1959. Tonadas de carácter popular chileno.
    Botto, Carlos, 1923-2004. Sonatinas, piano, op. 9.
    Arnold, Malcolm. Quintets, flute, horn, bassoon, violin, viola, op. 7.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Songs from William Shakespeare.
    Skalkottas, Nikos, 1904-1949. String trio.
    Gow, Dorothy. String quartet.
    Bennett, Richard Rodney. Improvisations.
    Skalkottas, Nikos, 1904-1949; Lutosławski, Witold, 1913-1994; Wood, Hugh; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Arnold, Malcolm; Allende, Pedro Humberto, 1885-1959; Botto, Carlos, 1923-2004; Bennett, Richard Rodney; Gow, Dorothy; Davies, Peter Maxwell, 1934-
  - Nielsen; Damase; Martin, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 79)
    Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Chaconne, piano, op. 32.
    Damase, Jean-Michel, 1928-. Variations on a theme of Rameau.
    Martin, Frank, 1890-1974. Sonnets à Cassandre. Rankin, mezzo-soprano. Pittsburgh Festival.
    Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Suites, piano, op. 45.
    Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Aladdin. Selections.
    Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Humoreske-bagateller. Weis, piano.
    Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Sonatas, violin, piano, op. 9, A major. Telmányi, violin; Schioler, piano.
    Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931; Martin, Frank, 1890-1974; Telmányi, Emil; Schiøler, Victor, 1899-1967; Rankin, Nell; Damase, Jean-Michel, 1928-
  - Busoni; Pijper; Rainier; Mumma, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 80)
    Mumma, Gordon, 1935- Large size mograph 1962.
    Mumma, Gordon, 1935- Medium size mograph. Version (1963 or 1964) not noted.
    Pijper, Willem, 1894-1947. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 5. Netherlands Quartet.
    Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924. Toccata, piano. Ogdon, piano.
    Rainier, Priaulx, 1903-1986. Devotion. Cycle for declamation. Young, tenor.
    Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924. Piano music. Selections. Ogdon, piano.
    Netherlands Quartet; Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924; Ogdon, John, 1937-1989; Rainier, Priaulx, 1903-1986; Young, Alexander, 1920-200; Pijper, Willem, 1894-1947
  - [missing], undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 11, Reel 81)
  - Berkeley; Henkemans; Kox; Maderna; Matsudaira; Schuller; Takemitsu, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 82)
    Berkeley, Lennox, 1903-1989. Ronsard sonnets. Pears, tenor; BBC Symphony Orchestra, Berkeley, conductor.
    Henkemans, Hans. Quintets, flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, no. 2.
    Kox, Hans. Sextet for flute, oboe, violin, viola, cello and harpsichord.
    Schuller, Gunther. Music, trumpets (2), horn, trombone, tuba.
    Stallings. Gestures.
    Maderna, Bruno. Concertos, piano, orchestra. Tudor, piano; Hessian Orchestra, Maderna, conductor.
    Takemitsu, Tōru. Landscape, no. 1.
    Takemitsu, Tōru. Son calligraphié, no. 3.
    Takemitsu, Tōru. Son calligraphié, no. 1.
    Matsudaira, Yoriaki. Orbits.
    Matsudaira, Yoriaki; Takemitsu, Tōru; Maderna, Bruno; Hessischer Rundfunk. Sinfonieorchester; Tudor, David, 1926-1996; Schuller, Gunther; Kox, Hans; Berkeley, Lennox, 1903-1989; BBC Symphony Orchestra; Pears, Peter, 1910-1986; Henkemans, Hans
  - Mahler: Kindertotenlieder. Toldi: 8th Psalm. Van Hemel: Violin concerto, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 83)
    Hemel, Oscar van, 1892-1981. Concertos, violin, orchestra. Source does not mention whether this is the first or second violin concerto.
    Toldi. Eighth psalm. Roger Wagner Chorale.
    Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Kindertotenlieder. Fischer-Dieskau, Baritone; Berlin Philharmonic, Bohm, conductor. Salzburg. 1962.
    Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-2012; Berliner Philharmoniker; Böhm, Karl, 1894-1981; Roger Wagner Chorale; Hemel, Oscar van, 1892-1981; Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911
  - Dvořák; Martinů; Rachmaninoff; Skalkottas; Weinzweig, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 84)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Kaprichchio na t͡syganskie temy. USSR Radio Symphony Orchestra, Gauk, conductor.
    Weinzweig, John, 1913-2006. Symphonic ode.
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959. Sinfonietta giocosa. Knor, piano.
    Bonsel, Adriaan. Suites, flute, string orchestra. Bonsel, flute; Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, Goldberg, conductor.
    Skalkottas, Nikos, 1904-1949. Little suite, string orchestra. Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, Goldberg, conductor.
    Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Serenade. Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, Goldberg, conductor.
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959; Bonsel, Adriaan; Skalkottas, Nikos, 1904-1949; Nederlands Kamerorkest; Goldberg, Szymon, 1909-1993; Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904; Vsesoi͡uznoe radio. Simfonicheskiĭ orkestr; Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943; Gauk, Aleksandr, 1893-1963; Knor, Stanislav; Weinzweig, John, 1913-2006
  - Stockhausen: Kontra-Punkte. Sessions: Three chorale preludes. Messiaen: Four etudes, and Le Merle Noir, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 85)
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007. Kontra-Punkte.
    Sessions, Roger, 1896-1985. Chorale preludes. Fillinger, organ.
    Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992. Études de rythme. Loriod, piano.
    Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992. Merle noir.
    The container for this recording suggests that it may also include the following: Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012. Nachtstücke und Arien. Davey, soprano; Rosbaud, conductor.
    Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962; Davey, Gloria; Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012; Sessions, Roger, 1896-1985; Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007; Loriod, Yvonne; Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992; Fillinger, Valentina Woshner
  - Berg; Dessau; Erickson; Flothuis; Hindemith; Ives; Martirano; Rush; Webern, circa 1964; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 86)
    Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963. Concertos, cello, orchestra (1940).
    Ives, Charles, 1874-1954. Three-page sonata. Peltzer, piano. New Artist series. University of California, Berkley. November 15, 1964.
    Rush, Loren, 1935-. Hexahedron, Op.1. Peltzer, piano. New Artist series. University of California, Berkley. November 15, 1964.
    Berg, Alban, 1885-1935. Sonata, piano, op. 1. Peltzer, piano. New Artist series. University of California, Berkley. November 15, 1964.
    Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997. Toccata, piano. Peltzer, piano. New Artist series. University of California, Berkley. November 15, 1964.
    Webern, Anton, 1883-1945. Variations, piano, op. 27. Peltzer, piano. New Artist series. University of California, Berkley. November 15, 1964.
    Martirano, Salvatore. Cocktail music. Peltzer, piano. New Artist series. University of California, Berkley. November 15, 1964.
    Flothuis, Marius. Canti e giuochi.
    Dessau, Paul, 1894-1979. Requiem for Lumumba.
    Dessau, Paul, 1894-1979; Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997; Berg, Alban, 1885-1935; Rush, Loren, 1935-; Peltzer, Dwight; Webern, Anton, 1883-1945; Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963; Flothuis, Marius; Martirano, Salvatore; Ives, Charles, 1874-1954
  - Piston; Riegger; Sims; Turchi; Wilson; Wuorinen; Wyner, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 87)
    Wyner, Yehudi, 1929- Serenade, piano, winds, strings. Baker, flute; Wyner, piano; Torkanowsky, conductor.
    Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961. Dance rhythms.
    Wilson, Donald M., 1937-. Five haiku.
    Wuorinen, Charles. Prayer of Jonah.
    Sims, Ezra. Cantata on Chinese Poems.
    Piston, Walter, 1894-1976. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 1.
    Turchi, Guido. Concerto for string orchestra. RAI Orchestra - Turin, Sanzogno, conductor.
    Wilson, Donald M., 1937-; Radiotelevisione italiana. Orchestra sinfonica di Torino; Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961; Sims, Ezra, 1928-2015; Wuorinen, Charles; Torkanowsky, Werner; Wyner, Yehudi, 1929-; Turchi, Guido; Baker, Julius, 1915-2003; Sanzogno, Nino; Piston, Walter, 1894-1976
  - Jones; Kirchner; Matsushita; Baaren, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 88)
    Jones, Kelsey, 1922-2004. Introduction and fugue, violin, piano. Bress, violin; Reiner, piano.
    Jones, Kelsey, 1922-2004. Passacaglia. Reiner, piano.
    Jones, Kelsey, 1922-2004. Scherzo. Bress, violin; Reiner, piano.
    Kirchner, Leon. Sinfonia. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Burgin, conductor. KAFE broadcast. February 4, 1962.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Black abbey.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990; Reiner, Charles; Utrechts Stedelijk Orkest; Hupperts, Paul; Jones, Kelsey, 1922-2004; Kirchner, Leon; Lennox Quartet; Baaren, Kees van; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Bress, Hyman, 1931-1995; Burgin, Richard, 1892-1981
  - Works for brass instruments. Nixon: Six moods of love. Poulenc: Fiancailles pour rire, circa 1962-1964; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3 3/4 ips; two track] (Box 11, Reel 89)
    Nixon, Roger, 1921-2009. Moods of love. Blum, mezzo-soprano; Gilchrist, piano. KPFA studio. Spring, 1964.
    Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Fiançailles pour rire.
    Starer, Robert. Miniatures, trumpets (2), horns (2), trombone. University of California Brass Ensemble; Polk, conductor. Hertz Hall, Berkeley. December 12, 1962.
    Leedy, Douglas. Elegy for eight brasses. University of California Brass Ensemble; Polk, conductor. Hertz Hall, Berkeley. December 12, 1962.
    Kay, Ulysses, 1917-1995. Quartets, trumpets, trombones. University of California Brass Ensemble; Polk, conductor. Hertz Hall, Berkeley. December 12, 1962.
    Dubs
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers, CB 185 (Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1904-1975. Quaderno musicale di Annalibera); Artia, MK 1562 (Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Sonatas, piano, no. 9, op. 68); Perennial Records, Per 2002 (Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 5, op. 67, C minor); Arturo Toscanini Society, ATS 1041 (Bach Suite No.3 - Toscanini and NBC symphony); American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers, CB 158-159 (Piston, Walter, 1894-1976. Quintets, piano, violins (2), viola, cello).
    Starer, Robert; University of California Brass Ensemble; Leedy, Douglas; Polk, Keith; Kay, Ulysses, 1917-1995; Blum, Margot; Nixon, Roger, 1921-2009; Gilchrist, Alden; Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963
  - Warsaw Festival, 1962. Lewin; Stravinsky, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 90)
    Castiglioni, Niccolò. Prelude for orchestra. Warsaw Festival, 1962.
    Webern, Anton, 1883-1945. Variations, orchestra, op. 30. Warsaw Festival, 1962.
    Mycielski, Zygmunt. Symphonies, no. 2. Silesian Philharmonic, Stryja, conductor. Warsaw Festival, 1962.
    Górecki, Henryk Mikołaj, 1933-2010. Choros, no. 1. Silesian Philharmonic, Stryja, conductor. Warsaw Festival, 1962.
    Kotoński, Włodzimierz. Canto per complesso da camera. Melos Ensemble, Kotoński, conductor. Warsaw Festival, 1962.
    Katuka, Stanislav. Permutations for Piano. Krause, piano. Warsaw Festival, 1962.
    Lewin, David, 1933-2003. Essay on a subject by Webern, for orchestra. University of California Symphony Orchestra, Senturia, conductor.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Concertino, violins (2), viola, cello; arranged. Southwest German Radio Orchestra, Rosbaud, conductor.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Berceuses du chat. Deroubaix, mezzo-soprano. Rosbaud, conductor.
    Górecki, Henryk Mikołaj, 1933-2010; Kotoński, Włodzimierz; Castiglioni, Niccolò; Melos Ensemble; Mycielski, Zygmunt; Krause, Ilse; Lewin, David, 1933-2003; Stryja, Karol, 1915-1998; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Senturia, Michael; Orkiestra Symfoniczna Filharmonii Śląskiej; Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962; Deroubaix, Jeanne, 1927-; Webern, Anton, 1883-1945; University of California Symphony Orchestra; Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany). Orchester
  - Petrassi; Stravinsky; Fukushima; Rosen; Ustinov; Britten; Nono, circa 1947-1959; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 91)
    Petrassi, Goffredo, 1904-2003. Trio, violin, viola, cello.
    Stravinsky in rehearsal. 1947.
    Fukushima, Kazuo, 1930-. Ekagura.
    Rosen, Jerome, 1921-2011. Sonatas, clarinet, cello.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Jugend Kantate. Ustinov, performer.
    Britten, Benjamin, 1913-1976. Charm of lullabies.
    Britten, Benjamin, 1913-1976. Folk song arrangements (1943-1961), v. 1. Salley Gardens.
    Nono, Luigi. Incontri.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Petrassi, Goffredo, 1904–2003; Fukushima, Kazuo, 1930-; Britten, Benjamin, 1913-1976; Ustinov, Peter; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Rosen, Jerome, 1921-2011
  - Reger: String trio. Mamlok: Variations for flute solo. Hindemith: Sonata for piano four hands. Korean Kayagum performance, circa 1964-1965; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 92)
    Reger, Max, 1873-1916. Trios, violin, viola, cello, op. 77b, A minor. Lydian Trio. KPFA. January 25, 1965.
    Mamlok, Ursula. Variations, flute.
    Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963. Sonatas, piano, 4 hands. Tharald and Dolores Borgir, pianos. Live at KPFA. December 19, 1964.
    Korean Kayagum played by Hwang Byungki.
    Borgir, Dolores Salas; Borgir, Tharald; Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963; Hwang, Pyŏng-gi, 1936-; Lydian Trio; Mamlok, Ursula; Reger, Max, 1873-1916
  - Bach: Die Kunst der Fuge, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 93)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Kunst der Fuge; arranged. Winschermann, arranger. Cologne Soloists, Müller-Brühl, conductor. Karthauser Church, Cologne.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Kölner Solistenensemble; Müller-Brühl, Helmut; Winschermann, Helmut
  - Schoenberg; Petrassi, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 94)
    Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Volksliedsätze. KPFA live broadcast. 1962.
    Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Volksliedsätze; arranged. Song 3 or 4, listing on container is unclear. With orchestra. KPFA live broadcast. 1962.
    Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Three short pieces for orchestra. KPFA live broadcast. 1962.
    Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Short piano pieces. KPFA live broadcast. 1962.
    Psalm No.1.
    Petrassi, Goffredo, 1904-2003. Concertos, piano, orchestra. Scarpini, piano; BBC Symphony Orchestra, Sanzogno, conductor.
    BBC Symphony Orchestra; Petrassi, Goffredo, 1904–2003; Sanzogno, Nino; Scarpini, Pietro; Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951
  - Seiber; Klebe; Badings; Kubik, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 95)
    Seiber, Mátyás, 1905-1960. Sonata, violin and piano. Varga, violin; Finnleisen[?], piano.
    Klebe, Giselher. Omaggio, Op.33.
    Badings, Henk, 1907-1987. Symphonies, no. 10.
    Kubik, Gail, 1914-1984. Divertimenti, no. 2. Francis Chagrin Ensemble.
    Varga, Tibor, 1921-2003; Seiber, Mátyás, 1905-1960; Kubik, Gail, 1914-1984; Francis Chagrin Ensemble; Klebe, Giselher; Badings, Henk, 1907-1987
  - Sibelius; Pauer; Reger; Koering, circa 1962-1963; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 96)
    Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. Quartet.
    Pauer. Quartet.
    Reger, Max, 1873-1916. Quintets, clarinet, violins (2), viola, cello, op. 146, A major. Michaels, clarinet; Endres Quartet. Sommerliche Musiktage Hitzacker. 1963.
    Koering, René. Combatt3n. Southwest German Orchestra, Rosbaud, conductor. Donaueschingen. 1962.
    Michaels, Jost; Endres Quartet; Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957; Reger, Max, 1873-1916; Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962; Koering, René; Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany). Orchester
  - Marie; Philippeau; Hamilton; Pijper; Henze, circa 1960; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 97)
    Marie, Jean-Etienne. Hommage à Julian Carrillo.
    Philippeau, Michel. Sonatine for piano.
    Marie, Jean-Etienne. Melodie.
    Marie, Jean-Etienne. Polygraphie polyphonique.
    Philippeau, Michel. Etude concrete.
    Hamilton, Iain, 1922-2000. Nocturne for two voices.
    Pijper, Willem, 1894-1947. Symphonische epigrammen. Amsterdam Concertgebouw Orchestra, Van Beinum, conductor.
    Pijper, Willem, 1894-1947. Violin concerto. Olof, violin; Radio Philharmonic, Haitink, conductor.
    Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012. Sonatinas, flute, piano. Gazzelloni, flute; Mersennier, piano. Warsaw Festival. 1960.
    Philippeau, Michel; Pijper, Willem, 1894-1947; Mersennier, Marcel; Olof, Theo, 1924-2012; Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012; Marie, Jean-Etienne; Haitink, Bernard, 1929-; Hamilton, Iain, 1922-2000; Beinum, Eduard van; Radio Filharmonisch Orkest Holland; Gazzelloni, Severino; Concertgebouworkest
  - Meyer; Winkler; Barber; Stravinsky, circa 1960; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 98)
    Meyer, Ernest Hermann. Symphony for strings. East Berlin Radio Symphony, Kleinhert, conductor.
    Winkler, Peter, 1943-. Seven piano pieces.
    Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Die Natali. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Munch, conductor. First performance. Winter season, 1960-1961.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Zvi͡ezdolikiĭ. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Burgin, conductor. 1961-1962 season.
    Burgin, Richard, 1892-1981; Winkler, Peter, 1943-; Munch, Charles, 1891-1968; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Kleinert, Rolf; Meyer, Ernest Hermann; Berliner Rundfunk. Sinfonie-Orchester; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981
  - Brenta; Chevreuille; Absil; Stockhausen, circa 1961; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 99)
    Brenta, Gaston, 1902-1969. Braggart soldier suite. Belgian Society of Wind Instruments. KPFA broadcast. July 26, 1961.
    Chevreuille, Raymond, 1901-1976. Serenade, flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, op. 65. Belgian Society of Wind Instruments. KPFA broadcast. July 26, 1961.
    Absil, Jean, 1893-1974. Sonatinas, piano, no. 2, op. 37; arranged. Belgian Society of Wind Instruments. KPFA broadcast. July 26, 1961.
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007. Gruppen. Southwest Radio Orchestra, Rosbaud, Boulez, and Stockhausen, conductors.
    Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962; Chevreuille, Raymond, 1901-1976; Brenta, Gaston, 1902-1969; Boulez, Pierre, 1925-; Belgian Society of Wind Instruments; Absil, Jean, 1893-1974; Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany). Orchester; Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007
  - Fortner; Canino; Schat; Petrassi; Donatoni, circa 1960; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 100)
    Fortner, Wolfgang, 1907-1987. Aulodie. Cologne Orchestra, Erede, conductor.
    Canino, Bruno. Concerto da camera No.2. Italian Radio Orchestra (Milan), Sanzogno, conductor.
    Schat, Peter, 1935-2003. Concerto da camera.
    Unannounced piece for orchestra (Italian?).
    Petrassi, Goffredo, 1904-2003. Serenades, harpsichord, flute, percussion, viola, double bass. Radio Italiana.
    Donatoni, Franco, 1927-2000. Strophes. RAI Orchestra, Antonellini, conductor. First performance. 1960.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: Contemporary Records, M 6501 (Busoni: Sonatina No. 1: Eduard Steuermann).
    Radiotelevisione italiana. Orchestra sinfonica di Milano; Antonellini, Nino; Donatoni, Franco, 1927-2000; Petrassi, Goffredo, 1904–2003; Schat, Peter, 1935-2003; Sanzogno, Nino; Canino, Bruno; Kölner Rundfunk-Sinfonie-Orchester; Fortner, Wolfgang, 1907-1987; Erede, Alberto
  - Ruggles; Riegger; Rochberg; Irino; Haieff, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 101)
    Ruggles, Carl, 1876-1971. Men and angels. Angels. U.C. Berkeley Brass Ensemble, Polk, conductor.
    Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961. Nonet, trumpets (3), horns (2), trombones (3), tuba, op. 49. U.C. Berkeley Brass Ensemble, Polk, conductor.
    Rochberg, George. Bagatelles, piano. Rochberg, piano. Recording from a (unnamed) festival.
    Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980. Concerto for strings. Japanese ensemble.
    Haieff, Alexei, 1914-1994. Symphonies, no. 3. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Munch, conductor. First Boston performance.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: Fantasy, 5010 (Denny: Partita for Organ: Lawrence Moe).
    Polk, Keith; Haieff, Alexei, 1914-1994; Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980; Munch, Charles, 1891-1968; Rochberg, George; Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961; Ruggles, Carl, 1876-1971; University of California Brass Ensemble; Boston Symphony Orchestra
  - Rush; Oliveros; Erickson; Miyashita, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 102)
    Rush, Loren, 1935-. Serenade for violin and viola.
    Oliveros, Pauline, 1932- Trios, piano, 4 hands, flute.
    Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997. Toccata, piano. Pelzer, piano. KPFA broadcast. June 13, 1962.
    Miyashita, Shūretsu, 1909-1993. Suite for Japanese instruments.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: CRI, 131 (Sessions: Symphony No.1 - Japan Philharmonic - Watanabe.
    Rush, Loren, 1935-; Miyashita, Shūretsu, 1909-1993; Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997; Pelzer, Dwight; Oliveros, Pauline, 1932-
  - Schuller: String quartet. Imbrie: Legend for orchestra. Nono: Sul ponte di Hiroshima, circa 1965; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 11, Reel 103)
    Imbrie, Andrew, 1921-2007. Legend. San Francisco Symphony, Jorda, conductor.
    Schuller, Gunther. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 1.
    Nono, Luigi. Canti di vita e d'amore. Dorow, soprano; Lewis, tenor; London Symphony Orchestra, Pritchard, conductor. Edinburgh Festival. First performance. BBC. 1965.